I lost myself on a cool damp night
I gave myself in that misty light
Was hypnotized by a strange delight
Under a lilac tree
 
I made wine from the lilac tree
Put my heart in it's recipe
It makes me see what I want to see
And be who I want to be
 
When I think more than I ought to think
And do things I never should do
I drink much more that I ought to drink
Because it brings me back you...
 
Lilac wine is sweet and heady
Like my love
Lilac wine, I feel unsteady
Like my love
 
Listen me, I cannot see clearly
Isn't that she, coming near here?
 
Lilac wine is sweet and heady
Where's my love?
Lilac wine, I feel unready
Where's my love?
 
Listen me, why is everything so hazy?
Isn't that she, or am I just going crazy, dear?
 
Lilac wine is sweet and heady
Where's my love?
I, I feel unready for my love