When we're driving
You say you can go faster, and
When we're singing to the radio
You say you can make it louder
 
And you roll another one
You wanna get higher, and
When I need the fire
You're always my lighter
 
When we're rolling
You always put your feet on mine, and
When I'm running away
You always remind, all the time
When I'm feeling low
You lift me to the moon and back
Back into your arms, I won't let go
Until I know how much you really love me, baby
 
I see a light
 
And I've heard we never truly see ourselves
You gotta leave it up to someone else
To know how beautiful you really are, baby
We never get to see ourselves
Sleeping peacefully next to the ones that we love
We never see us cry in someone eyes, see us cry
Someone who was born, baby
 
When we're driving
You say you can go faster, and
When we're singing to the radio
You say you turn make it louder
 
And you roll another one
You wanna get higher, and
When I need the fire
You're always my lighter
 
I see a light coming towards me
Moving slowly, but coming quickly
At the same time, I think it represents
What's going on in my mind, when
We're together, everything is so sweet
There's nowhere in the world I'd rather be
I could leave you, I don't need nothing but you
We're starting up beyond just us two
Forever it gets complicated
You don't have to be that way, baby
 
I see a light coming towards me
Moving slowly, but coming quickly
At the same time, I think it represents
What's going on in my mind
https://lyricstranslate.com/ru/miley-cyrus-lighter-lyrics.html