Mmm, mmm, mmm
 
Flowers in hand, waiting for me
Every word in poetry
Won't call me by name, only "baby"
The more that you give, the less that I need
Everyone says I look happy
When it feels right
 
I know that you're wrong for me
Gonna wish we never met on the day I leave
I brought you down to your knees
'Cause they say that misery loves company
It's not your fault I ruin everything
And it's not your fault I can't be what you need
Baby, angels like you can't fly down hell with me
 
I'm everything they said I would be
La, la, la
I'm everything they said I would be
 
I'll put you down slow, love you goodbye
Before you let go just one more time
Take off your clothes, pretend that it's fine
A little more hurt won't kill you tonight
My mama says you don't look happy
Close your eyes
 
I know that you're wrong for me
Gonna wish we never met on the day I leave
I brought you down to your knees
'Cause they say that misery loves company
It's not your fault I ruin everything
And it's not your fault I can't be what you need
Baby, angels like you can't fly down hell with me
 
I'm everything they said I would be
La, la, la, la
La, la, la, la
La, la, la
Oh, ah, ah
Ah, oh
Ah, oh
 
I know that you're wrong for me
Gonna wish we never met on the day I leave
I brought you down to your knees
'Cause they say that misery loves company
It's not your fault I ruin everything (Everything)
And it's not your fault I can't be what you need
Baby, angels like you can't fly down hell with me, oh
 
Angels like you can't fly down hell with me
https://lyricstranslate.com